<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="CategoryPurposes.xsl"?>
<CategoryPurposes>
	<Purpose Code="BONU" Name="BonusPayment">Transaction is the payment of a bonus.</Purpose>
	<Purpose Code="CASH" Name="CashManagementTransfer">Transaction is a general cash management instruction.</Purpose>
	<Purpose Code="CBLK" Name="CardBulkClearing"> A Service that is settling money for a bulk of card transactions, while referring to a specific transaction file or other information like terminal ID, card acceptor ID or other transaction details.</Purpose>
	<Purpose Code="CCRD" Name="CreditCardPayment">Transaction is related to a payment of credit card.</Purpose>
	<Purpose Code="CORT" Name="TradeSettlementPayment">Transaction is related to settlement of a trade, eg a foreign exchange deal or a securities transaction.</Purpose>
	<Purpose Code="DCRD" Name="DebitCardPayment">Transaction is related to a payment of debit card.</Purpose>
	<Purpose Code="DIVI" Name="Dividend">Transaction is the payment of dividends.</Purpose>
	<Purpose Code="DVPM" Name="DeliverAgainstPayment">Code used to pre-advise the account servicer of a forthcoming deliver against payment instruction.</Purpose>
	<Purpose Code="EPAY" Name="Epayment">Transaction is related to ePayment.</Purpose>
	<Purpose Code="FCIN" Name="FeeCollectionAndInterest">Transaction is related to the payment of a fee and interest.</Purpose>
	<Purpose Code="FCOL" Name="FeeCollection">A Service that is settling card transaction related fees between two parties.</Purpose>
	<Purpose Code="GP2P" Name="Person to Person Payment">General Person-to-Person Payment. Debtor and Creditor are natural persons.</Purpose>
	<Purpose Code="GOVT" Name="GovernmentPayment">Transaction is a payment to or from a government department.</Purpose>
	<Purpose Code="HEDG" Name="Hedging">Transaction is related to the payment of a hedging operation.</Purpose>
	<Purpose Code="ICCP" Name="IrrevocableCreditCardPayment">Transaction is reimbursement of credit card payment.</Purpose>
	<Purpose Code="IDCP" Name="IrrevocableDebitCardPayment">Transaction is reimbursement of debit card payment.</Purpose>
	<Purpose Code="INTC" Name="IntraCompanyPayment">Transaction is an intra-company payment, ie, a payment between two companies belonging to the same group.</Purpose>
	<Purpose Code="INTE" Name="Interest">Transaction is the payment of interest.</Purpose>
	<Purpose Code="LBOX" Name="Lockbox Transactions">Transaction is related to identify cash handling via Night Safe or Lockbox by bank or vendor on behalf of a physical store.</Purpose>
	<Purpose Code="LOAN" Name="Loan">Transaction is related to the transfer of a loan to a borrower.</Purpose>
	<Purpose Code="MP2B" Name="Commercial">Mobile P2B Payment</Purpose>
	<Purpose Code="MP2P" Name="Consumer">Mobile P2P Payment</Purpose>
	<Purpose Code="OTHR" Name="OtherPayment">Other payment purpose.</Purpose>
	<Purpose Code="PENS" Name="PensionPayment">Transaction is the payment of pension.</Purpose>
	<Purpose Code="RPRE" Name="Represented">Collection used to re-present previously reversed or returned direct debit transactions.</Purpose>
	<Purpose Code="RRCT" Name="ReimbursementReceivedCreditTransfer">Transaction is related to a reimbursement for commercial reasons of a correctly received credit transfer.</Purpose>
	<Purpose Code="RVPM" Name="ReceiveAgainstPayment">Code used to pre-advise the account servicer of a forthcoming receive against payment instruction.</Purpose>
	<Purpose Code="SALA" Name="SalaryPayment">Transaction is the payment of salaries.</Purpose>
	<Purpose Code="SECU" Name="Securities">Transaction is the payment of securities.</Purpose>
	<Purpose Code="SSBE" Name="SocialSecurityBenefit">Transaction is a social security benefit, ie payment made by a government to support individuals.</Purpose>
	<Purpose Code="SUPP" Name="SupplierPayment">Transaction is related to a payment to a supplier.</Purpose>
	<Purpose Code="TAXS" Name="TaxPayment">Transaction is the payment of taxes.</Purpose>
	<Purpose Code="TRAD" Name="Trade">Transaction is related to the payment of a trade finance transaction.</Purpose>
	<Purpose Code="TREA" Name="TreasuryPayment">Transaction is related to treasury operations.  E.g. financial contract settlement.</Purpose>
	<Purpose Code="VATX" Name="ValueAddedTaxPayment">Transaction is the payment of value added tax.</Purpose>
	<Purpose Code="WHLD" Name="WithHolding">Transaction is the payment of withholding tax.</Purpose>
</CategoryPurposes>